<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aditya Pawar</title>
    <link>http://adityapawar.co.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aditya Pawar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 10:08:44 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://adityapawar.co.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to create a virtual environment in python3?</title>
      <link>http://adityapawar.co.in/posts/virtual_env/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 10:08:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adityapawar.co.in/posts/virtual_env/</guid>
      <description>What is virtual environment? A virtual environment is the environment which differs from the actual installed python and other system environments, which means that you can individually install libraries for the python programs and project in the virtual env and not disturbing the actual system environment.
How to create it?  Go to the folder where you want to create an env and write   python3 -m venv env it will create an folder naming env in the directory</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make REST API in django in less than 20 mins?</title>
      <link>http://adityapawar.co.in/posts/rest_api_django/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 10:02:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adityapawar.co.in/posts/rest_api_django/</guid>
      <description>How to make REST API in less than 20 mins?  Firstly make an virtual environment Then activate it Then install djangorestframework then make a simple project called mysite  this is code area</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mathematics 3 Resources</title>
      <link>http://adityapawar.co.in/posts/mathematics3notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 11:23:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adityapawar.co.in/posts/mathematics3notes/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics notes Here are some of the resources which would be usefull for solving math problems
 Desmos calculator : https://www.desmos.com/calculator  The classical calculator for plotting all the graphs
  Symbolab&amp;rsquo;s calculator (https://www.symbolab.com/solver/laplace-calculator)  this is the new post!!! Will add more !! Stay tuned and if you got any then add in the comment box</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Article</title>
      <link>http://adityapawar.co.in/article/new-article/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 10:21:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adityapawar.co.in/article/new-article/</guid>
      <description>Hey there!! new article testing only</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>http://adityapawar.co.in/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 16:43:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adityapawar.co.in/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello World!!! Wait!! Is it mandatory to say Hello World, every time you make a new blog,then certainly yes. Anyways let me start by saying something which probabaly no one will ever be reading on the Internet. Yes I am sure, it requires efforts to read, that&amp;rsquo;s why very few people read and write (is that so?)
Yeap it requires lots and lots of efforts that&amp;rsquo;s why not writing, lazy me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
